<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
    Copyright 2010-2016 Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates. All Rights Reserved.

    Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License").
    You may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
    A copy of the License is located at

    http://aws.amazon.com/apache2.0

    or in the "license" file accompanying this file. This file is distributed
    on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either
    express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing
    permissions and limitations under the License.
-->
<resources>
    <string name="sample_cy_gb_gwyneth">"Helo 'na! Gwyneth ydw i. Teipiwch unrhywbeth yma a fe wna i ei ddarllen."</string>
    <string name="sample_da_dk_mads">"Hej! Mit navn er Mads. Jeg kan oplæse enhver tekst, som du skriver her."</string>
    <string name="sample_da_dk_naja">"Hej! Mit navn er Naja. Jeg kan oplæse enhver tekst, som du skriver her."</string>
    <string name="sample_de_de_hans">"Hallo, mein Name ist Hans. Ich werde jeden Text vorlesen, den Sie eingeben."</string>
    <string name="sample_de_de_marlene">"Hallo, mein Name ist Marlene. Ich werde jeden Text vorlesen, den Sie eingeben."</string>
    <string name="sample_en_au_nicole">"Hi there, my name is Nicole. I will read any text you type here."</string>
    <string name="sample_en_au_russell">"Hi there, my name is Russel. I will read any text you type here."</string>
    <string name="sample_en_gb_amy">"Hi! My name is Amy. I will read any text you type here."</string>
    <string name="sample_en_gb_brian">"Hi! My name is Brian. I will read any text you type here."</string>
    <string name="sample_en_gb_emma">"Hi! My name is Emma. I will read any text you type here."</string>
    <string name="sample_en_gb_wls_geraint">"Hi! I'm Geraint. I can read any text you type here"</string>
    <string name="sample_en_in_raveena">"Hi! My name is Raveena. I can read any text you type here."</string>
    <string name="sample_en_us_ivy">"Hi! My name is Ivy. I will read any text you type here."</string>
    <string name="sample_en_us_joanna">"Hi! My name is Joanna. I will read any text you type here."</string>
    <string name="sample_en_us_joey">"Hi! My name is Joey. I will read any text you type here."</string>
    <string name="sample_en_us_justin">"Hi! My name is Justin. I will read any text you type here."</string>
    <string name="sample_en_us_kendra">"Hi! My name is Kendra. I will read any text you type here."</string>
    <string name="sample_en_us_kimberly">"Hi! My name is Kimberly. I will read any text you type here."</string>
    <string name="sample_en_us_salli">"Hi! My name is Salli. I will read any text you type here."</string>
    <string name="sample_es_es_conchita">"Hola! Mi nombre es Conchita. Puedo leer cualquier texto que introduzcas aquí."</string>
    <string name="sample_es_es_enrique">"Hola! Mi nombre es Enrique. Puedo leer cualquier texto que introduzcas aquí."</string>
    <string name="sample_es_us_miguel">"Hola! Mi nombre es Miguel. Puedo leer cualquier texto que introduzcas aquí."</string>
    <string name="sample_es_us_penelope">"Hola! Mi nombre es Penélope. Puedo leer cualquier texto que introduzcas aquí."</string>
    <string name="sample_fr_ca_chantal">"Salut, je m'appelle Chantal. Je vais lire le texte que vous écrirez ici."</string>
    <string name="sample_fr_fr_celine">"Salut, je m'appelle Céline. Je vais lire le texte que vous écrirez ici."</string>
    <string name="sample_fr_fr_mathieu">"Salut, je m'appelle Mathieu. Je vais lire le texte que vous écrirez ici."</string>
    <string name="sample_is_is_dora">"Ég heiti Dóra. Ég les upphátt allan texta sem þú skrifar hér."</string>
    <string name="sample_is_is_karl">"Ég heiti Karl. Ég les upphátt allan texta sem þú skrifar hér."</string>
    <string name="sample_it_it_carla">"Ciao, mi chiamo Carla. Leggerò qualsiasi testo che digiterai qui."</string>
    <string name="sample_it_it_giorgio">"Ciao, mi chiamo Giorgio. Leggerò qualsiasi testo che digiterai qui."</string>
    <string name="sample_ja_jp_mizuki">はじめまして。ミズキです。読みたいテキストを入力してください。</string>
    <string name="sample_nb_no_liv">"Hei! Jeg heter Liv. Skriv inn noe her, så leser jeg det opp."</string>
    <string name="sample_nl_nl_lotte">"Hoi! mijn naam is Lotte. Ik lees elke tekst voor die je hier invoert."</string>
    <string name="sample_nl_nl_ruben">"Hoi! mijn naam is Ruben. Ik lees elke tekst voor die je hier invoert."</string>
    <string name="sample_pl_pl_ewa">"Cześć, mam na imię Ewa. Przeczytam każdy tekst, który tutaj wpiszesz."</string>
    <string name="sample_pl_pl_jacek">"Cześć, mam na imię Jacek. Przeczytam każdy tekst, który tutaj wpiszesz."</string>
    <string name="sample_pl_pl_jan">"Cześć, mam na imię Jan. Przeczytam każdy tekst, który tutaj wpiszesz."</string>
    <string name="sample_pl_pl_maja">"Cześć, mam na imię Maja. Przeczytam każdy tekst, który tutaj wpiszesz."</string>
    <string name="sample_pt_br_ricardo">"Olá, meu nome é Ricardo. Eu posso ler qualquer texto que você digitar aqui."</string>
    <string name="sample_pt_br_vitoria">"Olá, meu nome é Vitória. Eu posso ler qualquer texto que você digitar aqui."</string>
    <string name="sample_pt_pt_cristiano">"Olá! O meu nome é Cristiano. Vou ler o texto que escrever aqui."</string>
    <string name="sample_pt_pt_ines">"Olá! O meu nome é Inês. Vou ler o texto que escrever aqui."</string>
    <string name="sample_ro_ro_carmen">"Bună, numele meu este Carmen. Pot citi orice text introdus aici."</string>
    <string name="sample_ru_ru_maxim">"Привет! Меня зовут Максим. Я прочитаю любой текст который вы введете здесь."</string>
    <string name="sample_ru_ru_tatyana">"Привет! Меня зовут Татьяна. Я прочитаю любой текст который вы введете здесь."</string>
    <string name="sample_sv_se_astrid">"Hejsan! Jag heter Astrid och läser upp det som skrivs här."</string>
    <string name="sample_tr_tr_filiz">"Merhaba, benim adım Filiz. Buraya girdiğiniz her metni okuyabilirim."</string>
</resources>
